I did say we will play Valheim today
because this is a very very very big
update, huge update, Omega update. Um,
Valheim came out with its patch 1.0.
I played this game originally when it
came out and when it originally
released, and you can see I have 300
hours in Valheim. The last time I played
the game, the Mistlands were the most uh
it was the highest level of uh of
content, right? That was it. Nintendo
Direct. Uh, is I'm not going to look at
it today.
>> Countless eons ago, in the first days of
his kingship,
>> I'll change this.
>> Odin united the worlds by the strength
of his arm and the secret knowledge for
which he had given his eye.
>> Damn.
>> He waged a great war against his foes.
>> This is cool. I don't remember this.
Deathless creatures older than any
others.
The world trees shook from root to
ground with their fury.
>> Still. Okay, good. Yeah, I was curious.
At last,
when his strength was almost at its
limit,
he drove them together into the 10th
world and split the boughels that
anchored it.
>> That is cool.
>> Then he left it to drift,
>> a place of exile.
For centuries, this world slumbered
uneasily.
>> Not full screen.
>> But it did not die.
>> Ancient spirits sought out new bodies as
lesser creatures fed on their corpses.
>> Oh [__]
>> Fattening themselves on the old magic.
>> Other beings fell into the forgotten
world.
>> Even men found their way there.
>> Uh-oh. As glacial ages passed, kingdoms
rose and fell out of sight of the gods.
>> This is badass.
>> But as the 10th world grew again in
strength, the world tree reached out
blindly for it, threatening the balance
of all the worlds until news reached
Odin.
Unable to wield his power in a realm he
had cut loose from his own, he looked
instead to Midgard, to the tribes who
kept his flame alive upon their altars.
>> This is really cool.
The greatest of their fallen warriors
would be plucked from the battlefield by
his Valkyries and born again in Valheim.
That's badass.
That is really really cool. Uh I Yeah, I
haven't seen this at all.
Okay, good. So, we have this frame rate
limit. All this is good. Level of
detail, all this is fine. Controller,
keyboard, and mouse. I'm not going to
even worry about that right now. Okay,
game play, all this should be fine.
Okay, let me turn it down a little bit.
And okay, audio, all that's good.
Accessibility, we're going to turn
motion blur off, too. Okay, gentlemen.
All righty. Graphics to the max. Oh,
they weren't.
Big dick. Big dick. Big dick. Omega
dick.
Okay.
All right, gentlemen.
Let me go and
make my character.
Um. All right. So, this looks about
right. And skin tone, we'll make him
pretty white. And for hair, what do we
have for hair? Okay, that I might go
with that.
Uh, I don't know about that one. That's
like [__] He-Man. I don't know about
that. No, that's silly. That's also
silly. This is silly. I don't want that.
This what? Nah. No, I don't like that.
That's a man bun. We don't want to go
with that, obviously. Okay. This is Oh,
that looks good.
Yeah, just basic long hair, long braid.
No, no, bro. Like, no. Oh, like loose
waves. I don't like that either. Ma,
that's masculine. That's not masculine.
That's a girl's haircut. Matronly. Okay,
these are all right. These are all
women's hairstyles, right? Yeah, this is
What the [__] is that? What is this emo
[__] in Valheim?
Oh my god. Okay, well, let's go back to
the real hairstyles. Okay, this is
ridiculous. Ridiculous. Ridiculous. No,
we don't want any of these. Oh my god,
they have a lot of hairstyles. Holy
[__] Oh, that one looks kind of cool,
actually.
Okay, windswept. That looks kind of
badass, too. All right, we're It's the
ones at the beginning we're going to go
with, right?
Honestly, guys,
I think we just go with this one.
I think this is the closest to my hair
that I can get at least. I mean, there's
no balding and long hair option, right?
Usually most people don't want that. So,
we're going to go with this.
>> Yeah. All right. And then All right. For
a beard, a mustache. No, I don't like
that one. I don't like that one either.
No,
that's pretty big.
No, I don't like that either. Mustache.
I mean, I could just go with this. I
mean, the neat normal beard. Maybe
that's the right option.
Oh, that looks really good.
That looks Oh, that looks good, too. The
short. That's actually Yeah, that's
basically what I have. Maybe I go with
this.
Yeah, I feel like this is the right
option, isn't it?
Yeah, I think I should.
Okay. Uh, let me just go through the
other ones real quick. Uh, no. No, I
don't like that. That looks good.
Yeah. Yeah. Now, let's go back.
Yeah, it was the short one, right? Yeah,
short. Okay, good. And then hair tone.
Uh, I'm going to just give him brown
hair. Should be fine. Like, right, like
that. Then blondness. Uh, yeah, probably
about I think that's about accurate.
What do you guys think? Is that good?
Gentlemen,
make him skinny fat. No, this is
Valheim. Nobody's skinny.
Let's do it. Too dark. No, I think it's
fine.
All right. Uh,
how's
Wait, I already made a character like
that.
Uh,
how about Zach? Just going to do Zach.
Okay, great. There it is. It just Yeah.
All right, we've got it. Turn on DLSS5.
yet. It'll make it look like Thor. All
righty, gentlemen. Let's start it. Let's
get it done.
And what is this here?
Um, new
and then new world. Um, let me see what
it says. Let's see. What are we going to
call it? Um,
I'm gonna just call it Aartha.
Okay.
And
I think we're pretty much good to go,
right? Yeah. My chud life. No, this is
good enough. Type in random seed.
Well, no, it it is a random seed. Like,
it's just it's random.
Okay. Put camera to higher area. I'll
change it whenever I'm in the actual
game. All right. Let's do it.
Aarth,
let's do it. It's time.
Start server.
Where are we?
Okay, this is just How do I
Okay, I can just start, right? World
modifiers.
Okay, warning. World modifiers.
Okay, let's just do the All right.
Yeah, we'll just do normal, right?
Everything is going to be on normal.
Now have access to the mini map. Yeah,
this seems like more [__] Let me
just cancel this.
I am not playing hardcore. I will not
ever play hardcore for anything.
Like I I hardcore to me is like the uh
it's it's like the opposite of fun.
Make resource rate 2x.
Should I?
If I do resource rate at 2x,
I feel like I have to make combat at
least hard.
I feel like I have to do both.
Less grinding. Yeah.
Not very hard. I can probably change
this over time, right?
Keep it on normal.
Let's just do everything on normal.
Let's do everything on [__] normal.
The way it's supposed to be. Let's do it
the way it's supposed to be. And that's
it. All right. And I can change it
later, right? Like I can obviously just
change this later on. Like if I don't if
I don't like it, I can just change it.
Yes. Okay. Good. All right. Let's see
this. All right, gentlemen. Let us
begin.
loading.
Oh, the trolls.
Isn't it crazy that like this game came
out during COVID originally and like now
it's finally released?
2x Resources is failing the marshmallow
test. What do you mean by that?
Long ago, the all father Odin united the
worlds. He threw down his foes and cast
them into the 10th world. Then split the
boughs in which held their prison to the
world tree and left it to drift
unanchored a place of exile. For
centuries, this world slumbered
uneasily, but did not die. As glacial
ages passed, kingdoms rose and fell out
of the sight of gods. When Odin heard
his enemies were growing once again in
strength, he looked to Midgard and sent
his Valkyries to scour the battlefields
for the greatest of their warriors. Dead
to the world, they would be born again
in Valheim.
Few distance lags it a bit. Yeah, I'll
I'll wait till it's actually in the game
before I make a decision.
Damn.
I'm like this, bro. I'm like this.
I hope we see corrupted up here. I don't
know what I don't know what's in the
last zone. I have no idea.
Can I move around? Oh, I can.
Oh [__]
They're going to drop me off. You play
Ashlands? I did not.
Damn, I didn't even take fall damage. I
have arrived. Okay. Uh I'm Hugan to
guide you. Megalis. Okay. Sacrificial
stones. Okay. Got it. And this is the
new one. Okay. Let me talk to him. Get
your first spray. Damn, look at all
these bosses.
Yo [__]
Oh, that's the that's Oh, I remember
him. I remember this one. That's the
deal. Oh, what the [__]
Oh, [__]
This is the one. This is the one I don't
remember.
Okay.
Okay. So, first thing I have to do,
let's look at where we are on the map.
All right. So, we're near we're semi
near the Oh, I have to uh loot this,
right?
Okay. Uh let me I'm trying to remember
how to play. Okay. So, the first step is
we want to make sure that we get inside
and we build a shelter.
And I can kill this tree, right? Uh, how
would I turn off screen shake? That's
really annoying.
Okay. Okay.
That's That was crazy.
Both guys. See, I told her I I told her
I'd make a server with her. I I I'm
going to.
Okay. So, this is like a All right, we
need to go We need to get near the uh
the ponds. We're going to go near the uh
the water.
Okay.
Stamina is rough. I gotta get higher
stamina, better food, every Okay, I
don't want to [__] You know what? What?
What?
Get the [__] out of here.
Okay, we killed him. That's good. I just
don't want to run into anything
dangerous.
Okay, now we have the rocks, too. We got
to get these rocks ready so we can
craft. As soon as I get to an open area,
we're going to start crafting. Okay, but
I just need to make sure I'm in the
right place.
This is a very, very wide open place.
And what? Oh, what's in the house?
I can't [__] around with the bumblebees
yet. I I remember there's bumblebees in
that house, and it'll kill me if I go in
there.
Okay. So, where do I build my house?
Um,
what if I just killed everything here
and I just built the house right here?
It's like right near a lake. This is
kind of cool.
The island. No, I don't want to be an
island boy. Let me go over this way.
Let's let's look around a little bit
before we make a a decision. After I
make a base, I can never make a second
base. So, this is this is a a
Oh, look at all those deers and [__]
Oh, [__] What if I made a base here?
I could also just clear out that whole
area. Just kill the wildlife and then
build my own base there.
Dude, I think that's what I'm going to
do.
Like, [__] them, man. I run this game.
Yeah, I'm better than them. Okay, so how
do I how do I craft? Um Oh, wait. That's
a [__] I have to kill the
[__]
Damn, he had three damage to me.
Give me a minute.
He's stunned.
Get the [__] out of here. All right,
good. And that's how you deal with
these. I didn't get anything out of him.
All right. So, the first step is
crafting. Wait. Oh my god, it's another
[__] Give me a minute. I've got
to deal with him again. So, can I parry?
Like, can I parry with like my fists?
Let me see if I can.
I can. Wow.
I remember parry was like OP as [__] in
this game. Oh. Oh. I got items. I got
items.
Okay, good. Perry god. Yeah, of course.
Okay, so let me just look this way.
Hugone.
Okay, good.
Yeah, I like this area a lot. We're
going to make this the base. Okay, let's
go.
All right. And uh we're going to make an
axe first.
And then we'll also make a hammer.
It's a deer.
Come here. Come here.
Come here. Come here real quick. Just
Just real quick.
Okay. I can't.
All right. All right. We got to get
serious right now. It's a It's a boar.
It's a big boar situation.
Okay. He's dead. All right. Good. And we
got more food. Great. And we have to cut
down all this stuff.
First bore death. Why would I die to a
boar? I'm never going to die in this
game.
Like other people die because they're
garbage. I'm not. So there's no reason
really for me to die.
I'm going to just kill all these trees
so I have a place to to build,
bro. Die to a bush. I'm not going to,
bro. Like I'm telling you, like I think
the first time I'll die maybe might be
like in the swamp or something, if not
even later than that. Start with the
workbench. Okay.
All right.
Okay. Loot all this.
Valheim music is what you do done music.
Yeah, it it is really not. Like the
music in the game was always like very
relaxing. I liked it a lot. I'm still
deciding about the 2x resources thing. I
haven't decided whether I want to do
that or not. I feel like if I do that,
I'm cheating though. Like I just feel
bad for doing it. But then it's like if
I'm not doing it, it might take longer
and I don't know what to do.
Do it. It's worth it. You think so?
It's more grinding. It's cheating.
Who cares? I know settings aren't
cheating. You're right.
I always play 1.5. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe I
should do it just for brevity. But if I
do that, I I I don't feel I don't feel
morally
I think that it's morally wrong
like on on a on an emotional level if
I'm going and turning it up and I'm not
making the game harder. Like combat
needs to be harder if I'm uh if I'm
turning up resource acquisition, right?
Cuz it would just be wrong if I didn't
do that. Okay, so workbench. All right,
let's put this right. Oh, I should
probably make a like but here uh
categories crafting furniture.
Wait. Okay, so I can't Okay, I can't do
that. I'm gonna put it right there.
There we go. And how do I make Okay,
there. All right, so now we need Where's
the foundation?
Where's foundation? I got to figure this
out.
Okay.
Um
full. Damn. Damn, bro. Like, they really
want me to know that I got all this.
Huh.
Okay. Building.
>> It's a bird. I'm going to see if I can
kill the bird.
[__] man.
Okay, just use foring. No. No. I have to
build the base the right way. I have to
build the base the right way because if
I don't build the base the right way,
the crafting station needs the roof.
Okay,
give me a Jesus Christ. There's so many
items that they're giving me.
Okay, so what do we have here?
All right, show all.
I don't think that there really is a
foundation, though.
Is there even a foundation?
I'm just going to start building, bro.
Let's build.
I'm going to build like right here.
Okay.
[__] Is that where I think it is? Son
of a [__]
I messed this game up so many times. I
still remember the keybind for undoing a
build.
That's the one thing I do remember.
Okay,
we're going to do one more of these.
This is a big day for me. Okay, and now
we need to build a wall.
And this is only uh the first base.
We're going to build the Omega base
later, but I'm not ready for that yet.
Okay. And now we need the roof.
So, this is a roof.
And let's go ahead and put it right
here.
Oh, this is looking beautiful.
This This might be my best creation I've
ever made.
Do you do a random seed? Yeah, of
course.
And then we're going to put it right
there.
Okay, perfect.
So, now we have that taken care of. It
looks like [__] No, it doesn't. Complex
items, building pieces to construct.
Okay,
I'm thinking about this. Um, I I think I
do want to turn it to 1.5 into hard.
I think that's a better option.
But first things first, let's go ahead
and look at what we do next. All right.
So, uh, let's get a builder. Yeah, do
it. Yeah, let's do that. All right. And
then materials. Okay. Categories.
Uh, let's see here. Defense. Damn,
there's a lot of these, right? Crafting.
Okay. I need a cooking station.
Do it. Yeah. Yeah, let's do that. I just
have to log out and then I change it
from there, right?
Is that how that's how it works?
Okay, let me log out really quick. Yeah,
I want to do that.
What was the base game before?
Agartha. Okay, world modifiers.
Come back to hard resource rate to 2.
Oh, 2x.
Okay, done.
All right. Start the same. It was
normal. Okay. I didn't know.
Well, I mean the combat cuz I remember
the combat was like really punishing in
Valheim. Like you would take a lot of
damage in Valheim whenever you would do
uh you you would like not parry
something or miss something. And like I
can't imagine that like very it still is
really. So, like it's like very like I
mean but then how do you I mean can you
even engage in melee combat at that
point cuz wouldn't you just like get
instantly killed?
Yeah. Like I I and I'm honestly like I I
don't know. Okay, let's cut down some uh
let's cut down some trees. That's our
next step.
Get better armor and a shield.
Yeah, maybe. I've got to also get ready
for my food, too.
Okay, got all that. Higher star enemies.
You need a good shield. Oh, what's he
saying? What does he want here?
He found a snack. Consume it. Oh, did I
get food? Well, I don't want to eat
that.
Wait, I didn't get I didn't get any of
that. [__]
Okay, whatever. All right, let me see
here.
Okay, so
torch.
Just trying to get a get acclimated to
the game again. It's been a while.
Okay, so I can craft all this. I can
make a bow, but I need leather from a
bow. And I think I probably need to get
that from those [__] things running
around.
You can do raids uh on your base uh
instead of hard mode. Yeah, I don't know
yet.
Okay. So,
and I remember parry was like super
super super good. Like it was like the
most effective and like crazy OP thing
in the game. So, what we're going to do
first is we're going to focus on getting
I think let's go ahead and get our food
together because like I don't want to be
at 17 health obviously. So, let me go
and do that. How do I how do I get my
food together again? Uh I guess I'm
going to probably make
Fire.
Yeah. Oh, I need stone. Okay, let me go
get stone.
All righty. I think that should be more
than enough, right?
You need the rested buff. Yeah, you do.
But it'll take time. Like I'm going to
get that. Just hasn't happened yet.
Okay. And we're going to make our fire.
We're going to put it like right here. I
think that should be good. And then
we're going to build a cooking thing on
top of that.
And there we go. Cooking station.
Got it. And now um how does this work?
So cuz as I said, I haven't played in
years, so I forgot kind of how a lot of
this works. Cook item.
Okay. So then I wait for this to cook
and then I can eat it.
Coal incoming. No, I remember that. I
remember you have to wait for it to
cook.
And I remember you used to be able to
put multiple cooking stations on the
same fire, too.
Watch.
See, we're smart.
Okay. And then I'm going to eat that.
And now I get my health back.
Okay. Perfect. So, the next step is I
guess we're going to kill these things.
What are they called? Necks. Let's kill
the neck.
You can tame and ride a moose. Nice.
Okay, he's dead. And we need to get bow
and arrow. I feel like bow and arrow is
so good in this game. That's the main
thing I want to focus on.
I'm living in an African hut. I'm not.
It's a beautiful place. What do you
mean? A flint axe. Oh, that's actually
better, right?
Okay, I'll have to go and use that in a
minute. I think I need flint for
something. I forgot what it is. Oh, it's
like some like crafting bench upgrades.
That's right.
Okay, get all these
music soothing. Yeah, it's very
relaxing, isn't it?
I like it. I I've always liked this game
a lot. It's like definitely a vibe game.
Like there's a lot of games that don't
really hit that same that same vibe, but
I I do think Valheim always did. At
least for me.
So, how the [__] do I get Oh, I know
what I have to do.
I have to wait for these guys
and I have to go and kill the deer. I
have to sneak up on them.
[__]
Okay, got him. Anyway,
the [__] is this guy doing? Give him. I
got to kill him. Okay, he's dead.
Damn. Six damage.
That's no joke.
Okay, bow and arrow. Yeah, we're going
to get that soon. But I think I need to
get uh like leather to make the bow and
arrow. And if I need leather to make the
bow and arrow, then I need to get
leather from those guys. I don't know
who else drops it. Oh, maybe the boores.
Do
leather scraps.
Okay, that is obviously what we have to
do. So, let's go ahead and look around.
Oh, I think I can eat this tail, right?
Oh, I can't.
Okay, stew. Yeah, I'm going to cook this
real quick.
And I also have Oh, I guess I have
venison, too. The deer meat probably is
going to be like super effective. Does
the game have bosses? Yeah, it does. The
bosses are actually pretty hard.
Always get rested. That's OP. You're
right.
Let me go and actually How do you get
rested again?
Like, do you need to have a bed? I'm
trying to remember.
It's It's Yeah, it's it sit down. You
have to sit down.
Press X to sit. Okay.
Uhoh.
Wait. All right. I'm waiting. I'm
waiting. I'm being a good boy.
Next to a fire. Okay.
Resting. See, that means that I'm going
to be rested.
Okay. Let's see it.
The bed is on fire. Yeah. See?
Uh-oh. Is this like Power World kind of?
It's similar to Power World. Yeah.
This is taking a while, huh? I remember
this was a lot faster.
Okay, there we go. Now we have an 8
minute buff and we can use that to go
around and uh like go and like kill
things
and rested in this game. Oh, let me eat
the the the
neck thing. There we go.
Eight stamina.
And each different food has a different
bonus that it gives you.
Okay, I don't want to cut those trees
down yet.
Just looking around.
Wet is a debuff. Yeah, it reduces your
stamina regeneration. I remember that.
Damn, he died in one hit. Holy [__]
Did they upgrade the tree and grass and
foliage? Uh, I don't think that they
did. I don't know why why they would,
honestly.
Yo, what the [__]
What we doing with this music? The
temperature drops.
It'll reduce your stamina regeneration.
Okay,
this is a lot to get back to, bro. Like,
I forgot how complex this game was.
Let me collect all these rocks.
It's a big rock situation.
Okay.
Wet and cold. It's okay. Animals are
afraid of fire. You're right. I should
take the I should take the How do I like
How do I take that away? There we go.
Okay, good. All right. Um, let me go and
make a bed. I'm going to make a bed and
that way I can just sleep and that way I
don't have to worry about any of this.
Oh, what the [__] Oh. Oh, hold up. Hold
up. Hold up. Okay, that's one dead.
Who's next?
That's what I [__] thought. Get out
of here.
Okay, so now we need to think about a
bed. How the [__] do we make a bed?
And bed.
Okay.
And I'm going to put it right there.
Perfect.
Tidings. Sleep away.
The bed is too exposed. Wait, too
exposed to what?
What do you mean it's too exposed? No,
the bed's fine.
Maybe I have to build more uh more of
these.
Okay, we'll do another roof.
Okay, there's no way it's not exposed
now.
What?
How?
It needs a wall.
[__] Okay.
Okay. Come on. Can I just get it? It's
so dark. It's hard to even see anything.
Holy [__] Okay, it's got to be like
this, right?
I got to look at the other monitor.
That's how bad it is.
Jesus, dude.
Jesus. I can't see anything.
I literally can't see anything.
Okay.
Oh, there. Got it. Okay. Holy [__]
Jesus, that was so much harder than it
needed to be.
And then we have one of these
there. Okay. Oh, I I I think I might
have just done it.
Torch. Oh, I didn't even think of that.
Oh, it's too exposed. How do I get the
homesteader thing, but it's too exposed?
Maybe I'm going to I'm going to put it
the other way.
I'm going to do it sideways.
Oh, wait. Dead. I couldn't find it.
Okay, we'll put it right there.
There are enemies nearby.
No, there's not.
Where?
No, there's not. Where the hell the
[__] enemy at?
What? This [__] over here.
The [__] out of here.
Can't see [__] I know. Trust me. I'm
fully aware.
Just keep clicking it. Okay.
The bed needs to be placed near a fire.
What do you mean invalid placement?
It's totally valid.
Got it. Okay,
that's totally valid. It's completely
valid.
Hell are they talking about
bunch of [__]
Bro, I thought you were a seasoned vet.
Yeah, I was 5 years ago. I don't
remember [__] from this game, man. Yeah,
I don't remember hardly anything. Okay.
So, the next thing we need to do is I
guess we probably
we probably need to go and build
something, right? I mean, I think that's
the next uh make the uh the bow and
arrow. And the bow requires leather
scarps.
So, let's go find that. And we also need
to How do we repair?
Upgrade. Repair. Oh, I just click. Okay.
I forgot if it takes resources or not.
Okay,
so now we need to find and kill boores.
All bores must die.
What's this?
Oh, wooden door.
What the [__]
There's nothing even in here.
Yeah. What the [__]
Okay. Well, that that's great. Yeah. I
got a random ass house over there.
All right. Now, we got to look around.
There are no bores in the area.
What the [__]
This looks like an area where there's
like a [__] like something buried
there or something. I mean, like it it
changes the the music, right? I mean,
like, what the [__] Cuz I remember they
had things that were buried before.
Oh, I can eat these raspberries.
Gives me more stamina. It's a sacrifice
area. No, it's like a chain or
something. You do that.
Okay.
Make sure I loot these other berries,
too. That'll be really useful for me.
The ship graveyards. Yeah.
Just go around there at night. Oh, I
remember the skeletons did a lot of
damage. They were dangerous.
Okay. Run stone.
Nope. Blow is last. Okay, that's nice.
Does this game have a story? Yeah, it it
does, but I mean, this isn't a story
game. It's a lot like Power World in a
way where um you know, the story is kind
of what you make of it.
And it's it's a survival game. It's just
like p pretty much pure gameplay.
There's not a lot of uh Yeah. stuff like
this. Like there's got to be something
buried underneath here, right? There has
to be.
Dude, I want to Can I build a hoe? I
can't. I have to go do that. I'm feeling
very confident that there's something
built under there.
Where am I? I'm over there.
To save the princess. I don't think
there's any females in this game. I
don't know if a single girl No, I guess
the there's a dragon. There's a female
dragon you have to kill.
[__]
Where's this [__] at?
God damn. Okay, finally he's dead. Okay.
All right. So, how do I deal with the
deers?
Oh. All right. All right. We found
ourselves a boar.
This is a double boar situation.
Okay, this is good.
This is really good. Leather scraps,
too.
All right, perfect.
Now we just need a million better bes or
million more boores.
Make a better axe. I will. Okay, there's
three [__] Let me kill all three
of these.
Damn, they're really doing a lot of
damage, aren't they?
I wonder what hard how much damage do
they do on hard and very hard? Is it
just like.5? Is it like 1.5 and 2.0?
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Okay. And get a shield to parry. You're
right. Okay. And we still don't have we
don't have enough of that. Okay. And
let's make tilling the earth. Right. Let
me think about this.
Right click and hold block. Yeah, I
know. A flint spear, too. That'll be
good. I'm going to just make a flint
axe.
Look there, right?
Oh, boy. Look at that.
Okay. And
now we just need to get the scraps.
Oh yeah, I beat the game.
Okay. All right. All right. Lock in.
No,
bro.
Oh my god.
The other one body blocked it and then
he held him there and he died.
Oh, that's amazing.
Okay. Holy [__] Lucky. I know. I know.
I got so lucky there. Like actual
[__] plot armor. Wait.
Oh, it was [__] deer hides.
Oh, I thought I needed It's not even
[__] [__]
Give me a minute. All right.
We got to kill everybody here.
Get a bow. Here's the funny thing about
getting a bow is I can't get a bow.
If I could get a bow, I'd get what I'd
get a bow. I can't get a bow, though.
Like, I don't I don't have space or I I
don't have I need to kill boores.
There's no bo.
I'm worried I'm going to hit a tier two
bore and I'm going to get killed.
And I'm not ready for that cuz like
that's a that's a honey thing. I I can't
do that.
Okay,
let me get all that.
What's in here? Nothing.
Bro, this place sucks.
Where's my BS?
Where they at?
I don't know what to do. I just have to
run around until I find one of these
[__]
Oh.
Oh, that's not
okay.
M
follow the war. Okay.
Bad seed. It's too late. We're already
locked in.
We're committed.
Bore. Boore. Boore.
Absolutely
[__] mogged, by the way.
Okay. Oh, box.
What's in here? A wooden protection
idol.
Okay, great.
Nice to have that.
I can't see. Okay.
Um, move up there.
That's better.
Hopefully that's better.
Mhm.
Guys, I'm around the shoreline and I'm
not seeing any bores.
This is really bad, boys.
No board. Yeah, dude. This is [__]
I'm going to go up to the top.
Hopefully there's one up here.
Nope.
Um,
what the [__]
Oh, this is another area. Oh, I got
honey, too, out of this.
Oh, amber, I mean.
All right.
Dude,
how am I not able to find a single
[__] boar?
I don't even understand how this is
possible.
Where the [__] are the bores?
This is [__] ridiculous. I'm losing
my mind.
The flat open. I don't know.
Where the [__] are they?
They spawned me here for a reason.
Apparently that reason is to make me
mad.
Okay, this is a ship. I remember this
from the beginning. is that these
[__] things is that you would dig
down. I'm gonna put a [__] pin right
here. Okay. And we're going to go back
and I'm gonna dig this [__] up.
This is a big bore situation.
Parried.
Okay, how many of them do I have now?
Nine. Okay, now I can go and make my
thing. I swear to God, if I see like
three bores on the way back, I'm going
to be so mad.
I need the item from the boss you kill
in the swamp. The uh mist bone or
whatever it is.
Okay, I guess I should just go down this
way so I can explore. I might as well
and get some of these rocks, too. I'll
need more rocks.
Oh, I can't even loot them. Oh, I'm I'm
over inventory cap.
Okay, I've got to build myself a a
little base then. Or not base, but a uh
a thing.
A storage container.
IGN 10 out of 10. Crazy. Well, people
always really like this game.
When it when it came out, this game
popped off.
like it went absolutely insane.
It had like a average player base of
like or concurrent player base like 500k
or something.
Mhm.
Is it bigger than Power World?
Um
I don't I I think Pow World's bigger. I
I think I don't know.
I'm not really sure.
This game's a lot different than Pow
World.
I think if you had to ask me, I'd
probably say I like Power World more,
but I like this game a lot, too.
I don't want people to get the wrong
impression.
Okay, now it's time to make the bow.
There we [__] go. And now we make
arrows.
Mhm.
She went into a hobo hut. No, it's fine.
And I might cut down a tree or two.
That way I um
Damn, this took a while.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well,
that's great.
That's amazing. I'm so happy it
happened.
By the way, that was total [__]
Absolute complete and total [__]
I should have never got hit by that.
All right, we get big wood.
I mean, you saw how it switched up on me
like that. It start It was like going
whoop. There it is. And it just killed
me out of nowhere. It's [__]
Total [__] [__]
All right.
So, we got a little bit more wood
and now we're going to build a chest.
We're just going to build three of them
cuz, you know, we're going to need them.
All right, let's put all this stuff
away.
Uh, how do I put it in there?
Shift click. Control-click. Okay.
All right.
There we go. And also like we want to
make sure we cook items, too. Coal.
Wait, how'd I get coal?
The hell I get coal for
triple? Yeah.
Burn food. No.
No. I don't burn my food.
That's what retards do. I don't do that.
What do you want? I hate this dick. Get
the [__] out of here. Get out of my
[__] base.
I'm going to shoot him.
Oh, come on.
Okay, let me practice.
This thing sucks.
Oh my god.
What?
[__]
Okay.
Oh my god. Okay. All right.
Okay. Skill has improved. Once my skill
gets higher, I'll be way better. Okay.
We're going to kill that bird.
[__] I missed.
Okay,
there's a lot to cook apparently.
Copy your abilities. Okay. Yeah, funny.
Really funny. Close. Yeah, I almost got
him.
Is this free to play? No, it's like 20
bucks or something, right?
It's not that expensive.
Okay, let me eat one of these.
Okay,
there's so much of this food I have to I
have to do. It's going to take me a
while. Like, actually, you know what?
You know what we're going to do?
I'm going to do what I did
the last time I played this game.
Wait, I don't have any rocks. Where's my
rocks?
Where's my rocks?
Okay.
In your chest. Yeah.
I'm going to build like three over it.
This is what I did last time.
Okay. No way it doesn't work.
Wait, I think I can put another one in.
No way.
Oh my god.
Okay. Well, we we got we got three,
right?
Okay. Maybe I can put one like right
there.
Got it.
Dream axe. Oh, really? Really? Cuz I
just got four. [__] idiot.
Okay. Fuel. We're going to put more fuel
in the fire. I'm out of wood. No, I'm
not.
I'm going to kill this uh I'm going to
kill this this thing. This hawk.
Stupid.
I'm the I'm the master [__]
I'm the master Viking. I had to stop
myself there so I didn't say something
bad.
Okay, feathers. That's good. Put this
over here. More feathers. We love
feathers.
Okay,
after we cook all of this, we're going
to go to sleep.
[__]
All righty. And how many more do I have?
Oh, we're almost done. This should be
it.
I'll put this away, too.
And um put that away.
Everything else should pretty much be
fine.
Put that in there. I don't need resin.
Okay, good.
Let me take the title of gaming warlord.
What do you mean? Like I'm I'm doing all
right, you know?
Like I'm not that great. I'm just I'm
playing the game, that's all. All right,
deer.
So, how do I make a deer trophy?
Wait a minute. How do I do that?
Yeah, I'm confused.
It's a drop.
No, I got this. I got I got a deer
trophy right here.
What? I put it on a wall.
It's clearly not the workbench. Let me
go to sleep.
You need two. Oh, that's right. I forgot
all about that.
Yeah, I forgot. I forgot about needing
the trophies.
Okay.
You need bronze nails, bro. I don't even
have bronze.
I'm talking about bronze nails.
Okay, so next step right now
is going to be
um
[__] What is my next step?
Uh, I can make wood and flint for a
workbench or a tanning rack as well.
Yeah, I think that's what I need to do.
And how many arrows do I have? I have
70. Okay, I'm totally fine.
Um,
okay.
What?
Oh my god.
I'm actually garbage, bro.
And now I'm wet. [__]
All righty.
Yeah, this bow is like
This is rough.
Jesus.
Okay, I got to auto pick up. That's why
I didn't have one.
You got to get the blue troll armor set.
Dude, I don't even I haven't even killed
the deer. What are you talking about the
troll armor for?
Troll armor?
You're trolling me?
Okay,
let me think about what we need to do
next. I need to build the hoe.
I need to build the hoe so I can go and
and dig up that Viking longboat.
That's my next step.
That's what I need to do. Oops.
Yes. and and then as soon as I do that,
then I'll be in a much better position.
I probably also need to kill some more
trees, but I'm not ready to do that yet.
Okay.
Jesus Christ. Get the [__] out of here.
[__] you, [__]
Okay, now.
Okay, I'm not going to worry about them.
And where is Okay, so I need to make a
hoe. And I need wood and I need stone.
Okay, so where's wood? Okay, we have
stone and we don't have wood. Where is
wood? Let me go kill Let me go kill a
tree.
With a with an axe.
Okay, there we go.
You also found dual wield axes. You
know, I heard about that. It's like you
find them in like Viking encampments or
something. There was like a YouTube
short that I saw that says like you can
go get this. All right, we have to be
very careful. Logs are more dangerous
than the boss.
And I'm on a strawberry, too.
Like, for real? Yeah. Yeah. It's like in
a chest or something.
Like I don't I I hear that they're
really good, but like here's how I see
it. I mean, I just don't see how
I don't see how it's not going to just
be better. Who's this [__] that's
over here? These [__] just come
out of nowhere.
Oh my god.
No respect.
I got the bronze one. They're awesome.
Yeah.
Okay. So, now what do we do? Oh, yeah. I
was going to make the hoe.
Okay, we got the hoe. And I will do that
in a minute. Let me go and get these
place stacks. There we go. That's
perfect. And I'm going to put this stuff
away, I guess.
And I have Damn, I have a lot of deer
meat. Holy [__] All
right, let's go.
This is like Arc Survival. It's like Arc
Survival, but the game works. I played
Ark uh some of the guys in my old
classic guild played it, and I was like,
"Okay, well, I'll try this game out."
What a piece of [__]
What a piece of garbage, bro. Like, who
the [__] plays that [__] Like, it it
was it was so bad. Wait, what does he
say? I bring tightings. This tool is for
landscaping. Oh,
I thought hoes were for only fans. Well,
never mind.
Oh, wait, wait. I have to kill. I have
to kill.
I have to kill this one.
Okay, good. Cuz we need to get more of
the deer trophies so we can unlock the
uh the boss.
Okay. So, like maybe it's down in here
ground or wait.
What about dig?
Wait, I can't dig.
I thought I was able to d Oh, you need a
[__] pickaxe for that. [__] I forgot
all about that.
[__] You guys didn't tell me.
Okay,
thanks guys. Thanks a lot. Really
appreciate that.
Okay, he's dead.
That's done.
All right, I'm thinking Oh, let me let
me go get that thing of honey. I've got
to go do that.
Uh, should I kill that loser? No.
Oh, it's a boar.
I'm going to delete this boy.
Get the [__] out of here, [__]
Watch this.
Jesus. I You know what? I might have to
turn up the difficulty cuz I'm so good.
I might have to.
Okay, look around.
Shahu. Yeah. No, because I played this a
lot, right? And so like and I would like
my my main weapon was all Wait, a
mushroom.
Oh. Uh my main weapon was always the bow
cuz I felt like it was safer than the
big bore situation.
Got him.
Okay. I thought it was safer than uh
than the other weapons.
fight the tree boss again. I should be
able to fight the tree boss really
quickly. I just need to get back into
the swing of things and then once I
start understanding the game again, I'm
just going to be I'm going to be out of
control, honestly.
Kill this guy, too. I'm just trying to
kill all the boores in the area, too.
Oh, I got a bore trophy.
Watch this. See
I'm kind of afraid of the boss though.
Like I think I probably since I have so
much deer deer stuff anyway cuz I killed
that two star. I think I probably should
just craft myself deer armor. So this
right here, I remember this really well.
There's a [__] beehive here. And I
have to kill this beehive.
And I'm gonna wait. I'm gonna wait. I'm
not gonna go over there right now. I'm
gonna wait for them to despawn.
How do I know that? The exact reason
that you think I know that because I've
done it wrong.
Oh, there it is. Okay, it's over there.
Are you [__] kidding me? Okay.
Damn, there's a lot of [__] honey.
Holy [__]
Give me a minute.
Wait, I got to break this down.
I have to break it down. That way I can
I I can get the item. It's on the top.
Okay. All right. We have to activate a
higher level of thinking.
Did I get it?
Yes. Yes, I did. Okay, good.
I told you guys I know what I'm doing.
What's wrong? What's wrong? That's
right.
Okay, now let's go back
with the workbench. You can deconstruct
the whole building. Oh, can I? I didn't
even know I could do that.
Yeah, I I'll I'll have to do that next
time I'm over there.
Uh I I I was not even aware.
You can. Gives tons of wood. Yeah, it
does. I'm going to do that next time,
but right now I want to focus on this.
Okay. So, next step is going to be the
beehive, right?
Okay. So,
we're going to put the beehives
on this rock. We can't. It's too far
away. Okay. We're going to put the
beehives right here.
Tan wood.
[__]
Give me a minute. I have to kill a tree.
Give it a minute. We got to do it.
I got to eat a piece of beef jerky, too.
But I can't eat and chop.
I'll die.
See, it would have fell on me and killed
me like him.
[__] [__]
Got him. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh.
Mhm.
All right. Get my stuff back. Stamina.
The log of death.
They're really dangerous, man.
My axe is broken. I have a bonus axe.
It's okay.
I only needed one of those, so it's all
right.
And I'm going to cook things for a
minute, too, while I'm waiting.
See that? Oh my god, we're really out of
control now.
And I'm thinking about the leather scrap
situation.
M
I don't think I'm even going to make
that
I don't I think I'm just going to rise
above it.
You need to kill more. No, it's all
right.
Who's this? Go [__] out of here.
All right.
Um,
War Dogs, that's tomorrow.
I don't know why it says I'm resting and
then I'm not.
It'll go back and forth.
If I sleep, will that make it right?
>> Oh [__]
Oh no, my food.
Oh no, my food. Bro,
it says added coal times seven.
Oh, eight.
Okay, that's not good.
All righty.
Perfect. Yeah.
Can't wait for this.
All right.
All that's done. And
I'm going to make a pair of pants. You
guys were complaining about the pants.
And the next thing I need to make is
I need to make a chopping block. So, we
need to get flint. That's our next step
is we get flint.
What is it?
I'm just going to loot it myself.
Maybe I have some already. I bet I do.
Especially now I only need six. I know I
looted six of them.
Second beehive though. Oh, I forgot all
about that.
I totally forgot about my beehive.
Okay. Good. Thank you.
All righty.
I'm not very observant.
I just kind of do things as a train of
thought. And so the moment something is
like not
immediately in front of me, it doesn't
exist.
And there we go.
Perfect.
Okay. And now we can make
Oh, this is actually going to be huge.
So, I'm going to make a leather tune.
Oh, this is going to be massive. I'm
going to go all out on leather.
And let me go ahead and get all this.
Take all this out.
Okay, good
and
leather trousers,
helmet,
and a tunic.
And from now on,
I need to be level three for this, too.
I'm going to get rid of the other old
stuff that I have.
I think I'm pretty much ready for the
boss, by the way.
At least I feel like I am.
Okay, I'm going to upgrade my bow, too.
And my flint axe.
I don't really need to worry about that
right now.
Okay, what else do I need to do? Let me
get rid of this
rag tunics. We don't need either one of
these.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so not used to playing
the game. Uh it's been such a while.
There's a No Man's Sky update. I saw
that. I don't really play No Man's Sky,
so all that's like kind of new to me.
Okay, so the first thing I need to do
right now, I think that I'm totally
ready to fight the first boss. I feel
completely confident that I can beat his
ass,
but let's go ahead and
let me just cut these down. Yeah, I I I
think I am
cuz he doesn't do anything, right?
I'm going to make a shield.
Oh, there it is.
Okay.
[__] [__]
What a little [__] [__] All right,
that was perfect.
Okay, there we go. That's This is a big
wood situation, by the way, as you can
clearly see.
There we go. And I'm even going to kill
the stumps.
That way we can keep the area clean.
Okay,
there we go.
I got a beach seed.
Practice that parry. You'll need it for
the trolls.
Uh the way I do my parries is pretty
simple. What I do is I wait for my
opponent to attack and then whenever
they're about to attack, I attack or I
parry.
That's generally my strategy. I've used
it for a while. I think it's quite
effective.
Okay, so we need the shield now, right?
A wooden shield. And we need leather
scraps. Where are the leather scraps?
Okay, we don't have any. So that means
we have to kill Bors.
Let's go.
And oh wow. Yeah, I just realized I have
so much inventory with me.
Parry level. Yeah, I I don't know. Is
there is is there a parry level or is it
just block level? Cuz like if I remember
like it's been a long time since I
played, but
I'm just trying to see if there's
anything else I need to keep with me.
I'm going to get rid of that. I can keep
the honey with me. I'm going to throw
away the raspberries or not throw them
away, but just put them away. And I'm
going to put these away. And now I have
my armor. Okay. Yeah, I think we're
pretty much just like amazing now.
We have to kill at least our bounty is
uh five boores. We have to kill five
boores.
I'm debating. Should I kill deer on the
way over?
Maybe I should just to practice my
shooting.
How much gameplay? This is a full-on
gameplay game. There's like no real like
I guess you can say like there's like
busy work the game has. Like this game
definitely has a lot of like little
pieces of busy work, but otherwise uh
this is a full ass gameplay game. Ooh,
another box.
Okay.
And you guys said I can just build a
workbench. Oh, I I don't I don't even
have the wood for it. Doesn't matter.
Oo.
[__] got him. You just have to aim
over him and you'll be good.
And I got a trophy, too. I need those
trophies, by the way, because that's
going to let me um
Where's the bo
there?
It's going to let me summon the boss,
guys.
Damn. And there ain't no other bores.
Boore. Boore. Boore. Bo.
What do you mean he dodged?
How the [__] does a boar dodge me?
He would never know to do that.
Okay.
The [__] is this? I can't find a single
one.
talks
to the red stone. I know I need to do
that in order to find out where the uh
the boss is.
I think I am just going to go and fight
the boss though. Like I'm feeling pretty
confident about it. And I think that
like honestly I just go over there. This
is what I was thinking. Like I just go
over there. I just kill the boss, right?
That way I'm getting ready for the uh
the next zone, which is what what's the
most important, right? because then I
can start getting bronze and everything
like that. Yeah, just I I just beat him,
right? Like every boss is easy. You just
have to beat it and not get hit.
I think also like having the uh resource
increase helps a lot too.
I remember this game was definitely like
the one thing I didn't like about this
game was that um it was the [__]
uh the storage. The fact that you
couldn't craft from storage was like
super annoying to me.
Damn, dude. Where the [__] is this
place?
Look at this. There's just no bores at
Found one. I found a boar.
I found a boar.
Okay. Okay. Hopefully there can be
something good over here.
>> I I get a drink.
>> Does anyone like B Rising? Yeah, B
Rising was really good.
What sucks about my drinks is that I get
all the drinks that are nearby me and
then now I have like all the ones that
are outside of arms reach. I have to
like lean all the way over and get them
cuz all the ones that are within arms
reach of my [__] desk are gone. I
missed the bore loot. No, I didn't.
I'm so paranoid though. I'm going to go
check.
Wait, isn't that the one? That's the one
thing I needed to.
Okay.
Takes 15 seconds. Yeah, sure.
I'm drinking Dr. Pepper.
That's the good [__]
Okay, let's move this way and we'll see
if I can find
another. And if I get another beehive,
that'd be really good, too, right?
Because beehives give you the bees and
then you can like uh honey crafting in
this game is like one of the Oh, big
boore. Big boar situation.
[__]
Um,
honeycraft. Wait, what?
The [__] was that?
I don't know what the hell that was.
That was some [__]
Okay,
how much space do I have?
A relatively good amount of space.
I'll go check this area. Then we'll get
ready to go back.
You aim too high. Did I? Ooh. Ooh. Ooh.
Okay. Box.
Take all. I got coins.
Nothing special. You need coins because
there's a merchant that you can buy
things from. You can buy like a fishing
rod and there's a special belt that you
can bought. Oh, it's a deer. I'm going
to kill the deer.
The belt's amazing. Yeah, it's like like
me gourd or something like that. I
remember. I I remember because like I
had to make a whole new server to find
the [__] merchant because like I
couldn't find it.
Second deer uh had zero survival
instinct. Yeah, they're really stupid
thankfully.
Okay. And I have Yeah. Yeah. I have
enough to make my shield. And then we're
just going to go and fight it. I need to
talk to
uh this thing and it's going to tell me
where the boss is, I'm pretty sure.
And then I remember you find out where
the second boss is. It's like inside
these like catacomb things.
You have to upgrade the shield. I don't
think I do.
The only thing that's important is that
I don't get killed by like in like two
hits from the the boss. How do I dodge
in this game, by the way? What does it
say? Keyboard.
Where's dodge?
Block, jump, run, toggle, walk.
Doesn't even say dodge.
Block and space.
Is there any way I can just rebind that?
That's [__]
Oh. Oh.
All keys are bindable. Okay. Let me see
it.
Okay.
No, it seems like I'm not able to
look. See, it's not even on there.
Block, use, jump, run.
It's always been like this. It's easy.
Yeah. I I just
I never like that.
Maybe with mods. Yeah, I would
unironically just download a mod just to
bind that just because of how annoying
that is.
Okay. Um, now we have to focus on
getting over to here.
Make a single button that does both. So,
it's one click. Well, then I Well, what
if I want to block and I don't want to
dodge, right? I mean, you want it to
have two different buttons. Of course
like macros to your mouse and keyboard
make it a souls like yeah I'll probably
look that up and try and do that cuz I
remember I got super frustrated about
that cuz you had to fight a boss. Ooh
ooh ooh ooh.
Here we go.
Jesus. I one tapped him.
Okay. What's in here?
Okay, now we need to go back to this
area.
I'm at macros. Yeah. No, it's okay. I'll
figure it out.
Go ahead. See what happens. See what
happens.
I honestly like I I was going to ask
about that like I was going to like
message like uh not really message the
devs, right? but like just [__] tweet
at them or something. Cuz I remember I
always thought it was really weird how
like dodge was like its own unique
[__] thing that you couldn't rebind.
Like you can rebind everything but like
in order to dodge it has to be like this
combo thing. Like I I don't know why
they did that.
There's a suggestion channel on Discord.
Well, there's no way nobody ever said
that, right?
Okay, that is where deer is. So, now
we're going to go and get food. We're
going to completely buff up and then
we're going to fight the first boss.
Okay, that's the plan.
They added perfect dodge, too. Like, you
get a portion of stamina back. Oh, I
didn't even know that.
If I'm already doing like 20 damage on
my normal bow attacks, I honestly think
that this boss is going to be so easy. I
think he's going to get destroyed.
Unbindable G hotkey that sets up GUI
interface. What does this do? Oh my god.
What the [__] Okay,
I've never seen that.
What?
The [__] out of here.
You need to make fire arrows. Why?
Like, I mean, I guess I could for the
boss.
I mean, I feel like I don't really need
to, though, right? Let me see. Fire,
arrow,
uh, resin, and feathers.
Ah,
dude. I feel like I don't even need to
do that.
That's a lot. Versus flint arrows.
Actually, you know what?
I'm going to do it. I am. I'm going to
do it.
Give me a minute. Let me think. All
right. What? What? What? What was I
going to do? I ADHD.
Okay.
So, now we have fire arrows. Oh,
feathers.
Beehives. I forgot.
Oh, I can make 40 fire arrows. Holy
[__]
Oh [__] the beehives are killing this
guy.
It's like a tower defense.
I could just make a [__] beehive
army.
Oh my god, this is great. I didn't even
know I could do that.
Okay, so we're going to put this away.
We're going to put
Jesus. Okay.
All right. And then Oh, I need to make
more beehives myself. I got to go do
that.
Okay. Um,
okay.
Jesus, these [__] suckers are going
crazy.
Okay.
And they're empty as well. All right,
that's fine.
Now we're going to go to sleep and we're
going to get ready for the boss cuz I'm
going to have the bed needs to be near a
fire. Oh,
do that. Easy enough. Let's do it.
All right, it's boss time.
This should be really easy for me,
honestly.
So, what the plan is is that we use the
bow. Let's repair everything. And to
upgrade, we don't need to upgrade
anything. Oh, I was going to build a
shield. That's right.
And I want to get rid of
We need to get more chests, too. Uh, I
have so much extra space.
And I'm also going to get my food ready,
too.
So,
need to bail out. Ready? Why would I
need to bail out? I'm not going to bail
out. I'm going to ball out. What are you
talking about?
I'm just going to kill him.
Like, I don't I don't know what you What
do you mean? Like, think I'm actually
going to like I'm going to struggle
against the [__] deer. I'm going to
destroy him.
Like, it's it's not even going to be
close.
Like you're about to see like I mean I
like what what is he possibly going to
do?
It's a big deer. Yeah. And I have a
really big bow and I'm going to shoot
him with it. It's going to be [__]
easy.
Okay, so next step. So, we have the we
have the bow. We have the arrows. We
have the fire arrows.
And
now we also have the shield for parrying
if we need to, but we don't need to. We
just have it if we need. Make sure to
eat food right before the boss fight.
That's why I haven't eaten right now.
That's why I'm cooking.
I'm going to cook all of my food.
I probably should make two food stations
just so I can like min max and get all
this done faster,
but that's okay. I'm not going to worry
about it too much.
Does food expire?
It does not. Okay.
Oh, I got coal. Uhoh.
All right. There we go. It doesn't.
Yeah, that's nice.
I would say out of the survival games,
this does have a lot more of the um I
guess you could say like more hardcore
elements to it where like it it
I don't know like really the best way to
explain it, but um
I'm going to build another second floor
in here.
Yeah, this is way better.
[__] ass.
You know what? [__] it. [__] it. I
didn't even want it there.
No, I I didn't I didn't want it there
anyway. It's fine.
Oh crap.
I can do one more, too, if I want.
And we're going to Oh, no.
I forgot about my food.
[__]
I forgot because I got distracted.
There was a [__] distra I wasn't I
wasn't thinking about that
[__]
Okay,
now I I just heard it. I heard it. I'm
going to go and get it right now. I'm
going to get my food right now.
Okay, we're almost done.
Farm goes shut the [__] up, man. Okay,
so we have all this. Like, I don't think
we really need stamina food. I don't
really think it's like super necessary.
So, that should be good. We have our
bow. I think that we're pretty much good
to go, guys.
I'm going to be real.
I think we're totally good to go.
Honey's OP. Yeah, let me use the
bathroom actually and then we're going
to get ready and do it. Stamina for bow.
That's why I'm resting right now. I'm
going to refresh my resting.
Oh, whoa, Wait, wait. Is the food
burned? Wait a second. Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is
it Is it burned or not? Give me a
minute. Uh,
added coal times two.
Okay. Um, that's not what we were hoping
for.
Yeah. Um, that was not good. And we have
honey as well.
I'm thinking that we
I'm going to Yeah, let's do this.
We're going to use this combo right here
cuz it's only that. It's a small
difference in terms of that. Okay. I I
I'm I'm tired of waiting. I'm tired of
waiting. I'm tired of waiting. I'm ready
to start killing. Let's go.
Wait. I need the deer heads.
I can't believe I [__] remembered.
I actually remembered before I [__]
up.
Encumbumberance. Okay,
just going to bring them all with me. It
doesn't matter.
Let's go.
I will not die.
Yeah, this is it.
Go full parse part on. Not honest. Yeah,
I will. I'm rested buff. I'm totally
good to go.
It's trying to get me all these tips and
[__] I I don't need the tip.
I'm good.
Why no food buffs? Because I'm going to
save it for Actually, honestly, guys, I
should just use it right now. I mean,
who gives a [__] Let's just use it
right now.
Yeah, now we're totally ready.
It's annoying that we're going to have
to seemingly get wet
in order to get over there, but that's
okay.
Um,
let's just let's just go do it.
It's fine. It's only like 20% stamina
reduction or something like that. It's
not like it's like something insane.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Let me kill this.
That's one down.
Two.
Build a fire.
Uh, yeah, that'd be a good idea.
Actually, it would be a good idea. Um,
let me kill this.
Damn, they made these deers [__] I
feel like they used to be smarter.
Yeah, I feel like the deers used to be
way smarter. Now they're just stupid and
[__]
No, they was they was they was always
[__] Is that it?
Okay. All right.
Make the correct offering and the deer
will arrive.
Okay.
And let me make the
Wait, stone. I thought I looted stone.
What do you mean I don't have stone?
Oh, I have four, not five.
I thought there was a rock here.
Is there not?
Oh, it's over here. [__] piece of
[__]
What do you want?
What do you want? I hate these little
[__] bro.
They just run and [__] with you and run
away and then they [__] with you again
and then they go and hit you. Okay,
let's do it.
Big dick and all them.
Oh my god, that's all the damage.
Come on.
Objective. It's my fire arrows.
That's fine. I wanted to get hit by that
so it would move me back.
I wanted to get hit by that, too.
Run, run, run.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Got it.
Get the [__] out of here.
rolled.
Dodged.
[__]
rolled that.
I didn't know that that would work that
well.
I hit the wrong button.
Okay.
Okay. He's almost dead.
Got him.
I'm kind of [__] up a lot, but it's
okay. I'm going to take out my axe.
Let's one v one. Let's go.
Come into my domain,
Harry.
Get the [__] out of here. That's right.
That's right. Jesus.
There we go.
That went really well. It did. That was
great.
Holy [__]
It's bronze time. It sure is.
Not going to lie, I was enjoying the
game till I saw the boss battle.
The bosses aren't really
The bosses aren't the best part of the
game.
I'll tell you that
they're fine. I mean, they're not awful
or anything, but they're not the best
part of the game.
That's just the way it is. Just the way
it is.
Okay,
I'm trying to look and see where the
black forest is.
That's the next place I need to go to.
Oh, it's one of these.
Let's see what's going on here.
Nice. I got arrows.
Oh, I can actually change back to my
normal arrows, too.
Is that the black forest? Oh, [__]
Damn. Really?
Jesus, that was fast.
Maybe that's it. I don't know.
So, the main thing we need to watch out
for in the forest are trolls.
The trolls are the dangerous ones.
Very afraid of them.
And there's nothing here.
I just want to see if this is where I
need to be.
They're really And bears. I don't know
about bears. I haven't seen bears.
If there's bears, that's new to me. I
I've never seen a bear.
Are you [__] kidding me?
What?
What do you mean? I hit the [__]
tree.
Okay, got it.
All right, now what?
Let's look around.
You should domesticate boores. Sounds
stupid.
I'll just kill them.
Oh, that's a that's a big dick.
There's nothing in here either.
Damn.
Damn. Where the hell is the [__]
forest?
Where the [__] is this place?
What's going on?
We'll look around a little bit more.
I think that's the forest.
Oh, big bore situation.
Yeah.
Okay.
Rumor has it some traders have found
themselves in the tent world. This is
about the merchant.
Okay.
I think we just big dick him, bro.
Let's just big dick him. I'm going to
use my fire arrows, too, even
[__] [__]
[__] missed
fat.
They don't like being on fire, so they
run away.
This is going really, really [__] I
missed.
Okay,
this is looking
I mean if if you want to [__] around, we
can [__] around.
Go ahead. See what happens.
[__] you.
Got him. Got him.
What's that sound? [__] [__] [__]
It's okay. I have to stay focused.
Run away.
This is all going to be worth it.
He's dead.
[__] you.
Got him.
That's what I'm [__] talking about,
boys. Die.
There we go. That's a big loot
situation. You guys saw that?
That's what it looks like to be a
champion.
People didn't know. Now you know. Yeah.
Now we get the troll armor set.
We're going to use that for the next
boss.
So now what we do is we need to figure
out where the uh Oh, [__] I'm almost
inventory.
I'm trying to look around and see like
where a good place to build my base
would be. Do you guys think I should
build a second base? What do you think?
I think I build another base.
Yeah. Yeah, I think so, too.
Okay. Um,
damn. I didn't expect to see a troll
that fast.
I think we kind of got lucky there in a
way, right?
Okay.
Oh no, that's a skeleton. I can hear it.
It's so over. It's actually over. It's
actually over.
Okay, let me think about what we do.
Okay, is this a copper deposit?
I think it is.
That's a bear. That's a [__] bear.
That's a bear.
That's a skeleton.
I have to run at an angle. Some of them
have archers.
Oh my god.
Holy [__] man.
Oh my god, he has so much health.
Okay, I'm going to fight I'm going to
fight this. I'm going to fight this one
star.
Oh my god.
I will win. I will persevere.
I have to use bow and arrow.
I'm not thinking about the fact that I
don't have food. Got it.
Okay.
All right, that was that was not so bad,
right? It was actually really bad.
Dude, this place is scary.
I'm trying to think what we should even
do. Like, I mean, I barely even got out
of there alive. I'm thinking right now
like, do I just keep far? Like, you know
what I need to do? I need to go and I I
forgot when I get my portals.
Find copper. No. No. Good idea. Good
idea. I have to I have to actually craft
I have to craft something. I have to
craft my pickaxe. And if I don't have my
pickaxe, then I can't get the copper.
So, we're going to craft that. And then
I'm going to go over there with
everything that I need to build my base.
Dungeons copper and 10. Yeah, true.
All that should be really easy to do.
What the hell is that over there? Should
I go over there?
I'm going to go over there.
I think I can make it over there, right?
I'm pretty sure I can.
I hate this game.
That actually helped me. It actually
moved me forward so I didn't get killed
by the [__] uh by the the the [__]
stamina depletion. It actually pushed me
forward. It was actually good that
happened.
Okay, I'm going to look around here. All
right, two bores. Let me kill these two
boores.
The next step that we need to take is
do it. I hate these dick suckers, bro. I
absolutely hate them.
Okay, he's dead.
So anyway, uh what we need to do now is
living on the edge. Yeah, this is it.
It's pretty bad. Like I'm I'm kind of
getting [__] up already.
Let's move this way.
Greatorf is green. Uh it depends on the
the star level. The stars determine what
color they are and everything. That's
the way it works.
At least that's what I remember.
Oh, this is like a [__] Okay,
I can barely see anything.
Green is a shaman. Uh, yeah. Yeah, the
green ones are shamans. They put a
poison on you with like a breath. I
remember that all too well.
So, then we're going to go back and I'm
going to go to that same place and we're
going to kill everything over there.
We're going to kill the [__] Oh, I
need to make more arrows, too.
We're going to kill everybody.
Let's just say that.
I don't really need to actually even
help them. Aren't we going to make the
ogre armor first? Oh, I forgot about
that.
I totally forgot about that. Yeah, we
have 10 troll We have 10 troll hides.
So, that should let me make like
probably like what? Two items or
something. I don't know.
We're going to find out.
You pick the buff from the boss where
you can get the stream. Oh, no. No, I
need to do that. That's a good idea. I
forgot.
Let me cook all my food, too.
Okay. And
place the stacks.
Place these stacks. Place those stacks.
Okay.
So,
oh, I need bone fragments.
Okay.
You an in-house Aaron list. Yeah.
This is why I wanted to play with like
uh like have Kai do all the chores and I
get to actually just go play and do all
the fun stuff, right? And like she can
just sit in the base and [__] like I
don't know like build stuff or whatever.
Like talk to her chat.
That's what I was kind of thinking,
right?
It's just like a better It's just better
for everybody that way, I think.
Let me kill this [__] [__] Who is
this? They just run around like I hate
these [__] bro. Like,
[__] I forgot my food.
Okay.
All right. This guy needs to die.
Okay. He's gone.
After I get all this done, then I'm
going to go to sleep.
Oh, I forgot about my Oh, okay. Okay.
All right. Let me go and do All right.
troll leather tunic
and trousers.
Okay, so that's good cuz I only had 10
anyway, right?
Coal. Not coal. They're not coal.
So now we can put these on. These are
like a huge upgrade, by the way. Like
we're going from like one armor to like
uh
uh six
or two armor to six. That's still a lot
more, right?
Okay. Repair. Great idea. Thank you.
And now we're going to get everything
ready to move over to the other base.
That was me killing a deer.
Yes.
That was what I was I They put me in the
game.
later, [__]
I run this [__]
with the trolls. Yeah.
Damn, these are cool. I didn't even know
about that.
That's cool as hell.
We're on day six.
All right,
let me put this away. Put that away.
Um Oh, yeah. the pickaxe.
Um, antler pickaxe. Woof.
Where the wolf? Where the wolf?
Okay,
actually, let me double up on wood.
I'm going to make three pickaxes.
Here's why.
That's three times as long pickaxing.
Think about that.
There we go.
That's just smart.
That way when I'm done with one of them,
guess what? I have another one of them.
That's right.
I'm going to just make all arrows.
Make a workbench where you mine.
Huh?
No. I played this game 300 hours. Never
thought of that.
That's crazy. That's a good idea.
That's smart.
That would be how you could do it.
Yep.
That's that's one way to do it, huh?
Yeah, true.
Is it better in Power World? I like
Power World more.
Power World is like one of my favorite
games,
but I like this game a lot, too.
Okay, we got all this.
You sure letting a lot of people tell
you how to play a game? Nah, not really.
Damn, look at all that honey I got.
Okay.
And now we have to go turn this in.
Hello.
Here's the next step.
Uh,
I forgot.
Let's go over here. All right. So, I get
to have now I have the deer buff.
And the deer buff is going to let me go
fast. It makes it to where stamina for
running is decreased. I remember this.
And so, I can just use that and run
around.
Watch.
Get ready.
Jesus.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Okay,
now we're going to go back to the
coastline. We have the bow is fully
upgraded. Everything right now is in my
favor.
Literally everything like I've beaten
the first zone. We have this set up. The
ne All right, so our next goals right
now, let's talk about goals. The main
goal right now,
establish a foothold in the Black Forest
and we start getting better gear. I have
to find another troll to kill. I'm
assuming a bear will allow me to make a
pelt.
Why do I think that? Because that's what
bears do. Every bears have pelts, which
is going to be a cloak. And then we can
also kill the trolls.
And then we we we have to kill the
copper.
This is a deer. You know what we do to
deers? We let them run away because we
were too slow to hit them. Okay.
And I'm going to go near this open area.
You can make food from bear meat, too.
Yeah. I don't know how the bear combat
is going to go. We're going to figure
that out, though.
I'm a little bit honestly I'm kind of
afraid. I've never fought a bear before
in this game.
I'm going to treat them with uh with a
tremendous amount of um
I'm going to be I'm going to be I'm
going to act like I'm going to play like
a [__] Okay, that's what I'm trying to
say. I'm going to play like a massive
[__] And then we also need to be
thinking about, so this is another thing
that I remember is that you could kill a
shipwreck and there are shipwrecks on
the Black Forest and the shipwrecks
dropped fine wood and then you could use
the fine wood to craft the next level of
bow and it was like a super effective
way that like you could like leaprog
ahead.
I remember this.
So we're going to do that.
Now, I don't need to kill these deer. I
don't need to think I don't I don't even
want to think about the deer.
Not only do I not want to kill them, I
don't want to think about them.
And my shield doesn't have the shielding
properties
that I need it to. Okay, this is where
the bear was.
I remember this because this is where
the skeletons were, too. We're going to
take the bow out. We're going to get
ready.
Is this a copper deposit?
Stop, bro. Are you [__] kidding me?
This is what you would call a rock
deposit. They're similar to copper
deposits except for there's no copper.
That's a rock deposit. We don't We don't
want rock deposits.
Okay. It says copper on it. Yeah, that
one didn't say copper.
It's just a rock deposit.
Okay,
we need to be care. That's a copper
deposit.
I want to make sure that we're not going
to put ourselves in a situation.
So, I want to look around a little bit
more.
That's a [__]
That's actually an elite [__]
We're going to We're going to have to
watch out for him.
Okay.
Right.
Okay. No, it's fine. It's fine. I wanted
to miss that. I I didn't want to hit him
there. I thought there was a [__]
some skeletons here. There's a skeleton
area.
A box.
A wooden spear.
I I mean, I guess that's good, right? I
mean, I don't really want it, but I have
it.
Where'd that bear go?
There.
That did a lot of damage.
That did 23 damage.
That's really That's a lot of damage.
And that was also a parry, too. So that
means naturally it's going to almost do
my entire health bar.
And there's two of them.
I can't eat my food because I've got
these [__] attacking me. And I can't
get hit by the bow because then that
guy's going to kill me.
Okay,
at least I got away from that, right?
Jesus,
this is rough.
[__] you.
Okay, he's dead.
I remember the skeletons were pretty
hard to kill cuz like each shield only
has a shielding amount that it can
shield for.
Okay. And what's in here?
Check.
Troll. K. Seems like every
Okay.
Can I parry a troll?
Do I have a big enough dick to parry a
troll?
I don't think I do.
I don't
I don't have
I don't have it.
I didn't think it would do that much
damage.
Holy [__]
Jesus.
I just got [__] annihilated.
Okay, let me run back.
God damn,
you need a bronze buckler. Well, I sure
as hell didn't need the piece of [__]
that I had. I died in one [__] hit.
I didn't even have a chance.
Mark the copper on the map. Look, it's
it's over there.
Like, I'm not worried about it.
I'm just going to go over there and uh
and get my body back.
It take me a minute, but it's okay.
Get your rested bonus. Oh, [__] I
didn't even think about that. It's too
late now.
[__]
So, like here's a question I have.
if you're playing on like the very hard
difficulty,
can you even engage in melee combat?
Because if they're doing that much
damage, I remember how the block
multiplier worked and like
Yes. Well, you just But you you can't
parry though, right? You'd have to
dodge.
You need to be extremely strategic.
A good shield, you'd be fine. Like I
remember whenever So like I remember
whenever I was playing
[__] Okay. Is that No, that that's
fine. Uh whenever I was playing before
that I remember there were like these
big trolls
not trolls, but they were like the fuel
lings. Yeah. Yeah. Fuel lings. And um
whenever you would fight them, they
would do so much damage if they had two
stars that like you couldn't even block
them with like the black steel buckler
or like whatever it was like the the
best one.
Oh [__]
Oh, this is just getting worse and
worse.
That's that that the bear is new. I
didn't play with the bear. I've never
played with the bear before.
Okay, we're going to try to kill the
bear.
Use bow. No, no, no, no. I I I know that
a bronze shield, iron shield would be a
night and day difference. The devs
tweaked the damage values.
very hard start enemies. Crazy damage
multiplier. A two start an enemy is like
a four-st star equivalent or something.
Yeah. Yeah. I just
I like the idea of playing it on a hard
difficulty, but like if everything just
one-shots you and you're like forced
into like a you know a specific play
style that's like not really as
exciting.
Okay, goodbye.
Okay, let's kill that let's kill that
[__]
uh that guy.
That bear.
I've never killed a bear.
I don't know what to expect or what's
going to happen.
I'm going to make a rug. Yeah. No
bonfire to rest. I'm going to kill his
ass right now.
I want to put him to rest cuz he's going
to die. He'd be dead. I'm going to kill
him.
What?
It doesn't even do any damage.
How many arrows do I have?
Nine. Where? Wait. No, it's 109.
Jesus, that's a big boy.
These behave like the locks in the
planes.
[__]
Okay. So, he's like mad, right?
Yeah, he's mad.
Go
80 damage.
It's a lot of damage.
This is I'm going to die. I'm going to
get killed. I can already tell
this is it's over. It's over. I can
tell,
dude. I'm like barely I'm not even
making a dent in him.
Oh my god.
14 damage.
I need to get my honey. Let me eat my
honey.
It's almost half. I know.
It's like one attack can maybe kill me.
I don't know. Maybe it won't. And he's
only half health, dude. The bear is even
He's like twice as strong as the [__]
troll, man.
How the [__] is this real?
Jesus Christ.
That was dangerous.
The bear is harder than a deer god.
Yeah. What the [__] man?
See, I kind of want to try and melee
him, but I'm just afraid, obviously.
Okay, it hits me for 60.
That's a lot.
I have to be even more careful now.
I need to I need to kite him around.
I hit the wall,
man.
That is brutal.
Holy [__]
Just dodge his attacks. I don't know.
That's insane. The bear is no joke.
Yeah, I didn't expect them to be that
hard. Does his health reset or is it the
same?
Or does it like does it go back to a
[__]
Okay, let me eat my food again.
No. Okay, good.
All right, let's run back. Oh, wait. Let
me get my food.
I'm going to rest.
[__] spice. Oh, but it's [__] Oh
my god. Okay.
Rest bonus. I can't rest cuz there's I
don't have the fire in there.
Yeah, I didn't expect them to be so
hard.
I feel like I probably should keep
trying to kill him though, right?
I just I I I hate the fact that like you
have to press two buttons to dodge and
you can't just rebind dodge to its own
unique key. I don't know why you
wouldn't be able to do that
cuz like I'd be more willing to try to
fight him like in melee but um not if if
I have to press two keys.
That's just how it is. Yeah, it's just
dumb.
Okay, let's go back.
All
right.
Just hold on block until you don't have
to move.
No, I I just I'm just going to download
a mod or something that's going to like
let me let me do it.
Okay, let's go.
Slash the bear. Oh my god, that did like
half my health.
We We're going to try to kill this bear
again. I think I can do it.
It's going to be annoying, but
I already I mean, I already got him to
half, right?
So
I just need to do that again.
What difficult is this? Just normal
mosquitoes. Yeah.
[__] [__] [__]
Look at him. Oh my god.
See, I'm dead.
Holy [__]
It's a brute, too.
Try and go around him.
Okay, there's the stuff. And I don't see
the bear.
got it.
Okay.
Oh my god.
I can't put my armor on either. Yeah, I
can. I can.
[__] I can't move. I can't see. I can't
move. I can't do I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
Okay. All right. I got to do one more.
Jesus Christ. I hate this [__] zone.
What do I even do?
Do I just have to fight through every
single one of these [__]
Oh my god.
Can I aggro the bear and have the bear
kill them?
Jesus Christ.
Look at them all.
Look at all these [__] man.
Okay, how do we handle this?
Oh my god.
I can't move.
[__]
[__] [__] Is that a two star?
God.
Okay.
Focus. Yeah.
All right.
Out of that.
[__] I think I'm going to die again.
I have to run.
Jesus Christ.
The skeleton's going to fight, dude.
They're just they're just running away
like Okay, now now they're being
distracted.
Okay, maybe I can do something.
No, not anymore.
Okay.
All right. That's one down.
Two down.
[__] I can't see anything cuz it's in
the dark.
[__]
What?
Okay, that's another one down.
Jesus Christ.
wasn't paying attention.
I was thinking about something else.
Jesus [__] Christ. Holy [__] that
was annoying. God damn.
Okay. Um,
wow.
Let me loot all this stuff.
This deer hides, too. Debating if I
should even loot this stuff or not.
Probably not.
Okay, let's go back.
All right.
Give me a minute. Let me kill this guy.
There's There's four more.
Oh, [__] this.
[__] this. I got I got I got to eat food
anyway. I'm I'm hungry. I I'm hungry.
I'm gonna I'm going to go get some food.
Holy [__]
Jesus Christ.
I'm I'm I'm take a break.
This is ridiculous.
Chipotle hopefully. Yeah, I'm going to
try and get some Chipotle.
It's getting intense. Yeah. Bear equals
parry tutorial. No, it doesn't matter.
Like it's just it's going to do so much
damage it doesn't even make a
difference. They're mobbing on you. I
honestly
I hate the black forest. It's like one
of the it's the probably I hate that
zone the most out of all zones
because of the
like the mobbing that down of like all
the all these things. Like I I I
absolutely hate it.
You can't you can't see anything. It's
in the dark. Like, holy [__] Yeah, it's
just like too much.
It's annoying to me. Wait till you reach
Ashlands. Yeah,
the trolls are fun though. Yeah, the
bears are just so strong.
Like, they have so much resilience.
Like, I they added a AoE hammer for
killing the dwarves. Well, I don't know
where that is. I don't have that. Do you
want to be the bright forest? Well, it's
just it's like there's never two of
them. There's like seven every single
time, right? But where am I? Oh, okay. I
see where I am.
I just pull out the torch. I didn't have
one.
Yeah, I didn't think of it either.
Okay.
Spawns are increased at night. Yeah,
it's just it's overwhelming, that's all.
But I'm probably going to play the um uh
I think Warogs comes out tomorrow,
right? I think it does. I'm not sure.
Is that the case?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm going to try that
tomorrow. I'm going play it tomorrow.
You're just exposing
us on. I I don't know what happened. I
have to look.
No Man's Sky update too. Oh, nice.
What the [__]
Dawn Walker after Warogs. Uh maybe maybe
I would try Blood of the Dawn Walker
out. I don't know yet.
You can build space stations and [__]
now. God damn, bro. Like, they just add
new [__] all the time. Holy [__]
Runescape Dragon Wilds. Yeah, I like
that game. That game is really fun.
Holy [__] that was brutal. Okay, and I
will repair everything too.
Dawn Walker is a game you should play
off stream in my opinion. should play
Dawn Walker off stream. Uh, I'll
probably play the first couple of days
on stream and then after that I can, you
know, maybe play it off stream or on
stream. I don't know yet. Dragon was
actually pretty fun. Yeah, I remember
playing it. I thought it was enjoyable.
Close this.
Do you ever open to playing stuff like
uh Warogs with viewers or subs?
>> Um, I don't know. Honestly, I'm not sure
really if I would.
You have certain block power and you'll
take no damage. Yeah, I I know how the
game works. Like the American Revolution
game. Yeah, that would be fun. Didn't
even get out of the meadows. I did. I
got I got to the Black Forest, but then
I just got mobbed down and I I couldn't
do anything, so I I just I was like,
there's too many of them. [__] it. I'm
done. I'm tired.
How do you feel about dragon
playing through of Valheim? I don't
about quitting. I just uh there's a lot
of other stuff coming out and
sorry, there's a lot of other stuff
coming out and I'm going to play
whatever I can that's like new.
That's really it.
Too many games. Yeah, there's too many
games.
I think with Valheim, what I might do,
I might just go and uh
like since they I feel like they haven't
really added that much new stuff, I
could just play my my old character,
too. And that way I can just do the new
content and I don't have to redo
everything. I'm just trying to decide
it.
Is it going to see Deep North? Yeah. At
least everything on Musha's story line
on stream when it was time so VOD
watchers don't have another cliffhanger.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Why didn't you do that? I just didn't
think to. I thought it'd be more
interesting to um start from the
beginning again.
That was what I was considering at
least. But anyway, um I've got to uh
I've got to go. I'm going to get some
food and uh get a drink and relax and
I'll be back on tomorrow and we might
play Warog. So, thank you guys all so
much for watching. I really appreciate
it and I'll see you all tomorrow. All
right, boys. Peace.